



Birthday: June 25th, 1989 - Gender: Male - Marital status: Marriage Address: 13 Nguyen Dinh Chieu Street, Ward 4, Phu Nhuan District, HCM City

Cell phone: 0908.898.755 - Email: nndong89@gmail.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

I wish I have opportunity to apply maximally of my knowledge and experience on the assumed job.

Working in a professional working environment with opportunities in order to gain experience, develop myself, seek opportunities of advancement and success at work.

- From 1-2 years: Self-development, accumulation of knowledge and experience in System administration & Security:
 - From 2-3 years: Working in a senior position, participate in company's ERP project.

Having a stable and lasting job to participate in the construction and strong development of the company while enhancing my career.

EDUCATION

From Dec 2014 – Mar 2017: The 2nd degree, IT Engineer, TVU-TOPICA Viet Nam.

From 2007-2011: The University of Sciences - Ho Chi Minh city- Environmental Informatics

- Assisting teachers for installing projector, computer, practiced software in the laboratory;
- Graduation thesis was "Building Web-GIS popular environmental information to community" using JSP, PostgreSQL and Geoserver, reached point A;
- A collaborator, building database and application for air pollution management in Binh Phuoc province, using C# and PostgreSQL, a module in Provincial Science Subject.

WORKING EXPERIENCE

July 2018 until now: Working at KDDI Viet Nam

- Position: System Engineer;
- **Duties**: Working as a Presale & Implement engineer for SI projects. Some prominent projects that I have participated in implementing as follow:
 - From Dec 2020 until now:
 - Mitsubishi Motors Viet Nam: Microsoft System Center solution project (SCCM);
 - Mitsubishi Corporation: New Office & New IT Network & System project;
 - o Ando Hazama Viet Nam: Server Replacement & MS365 Email migration project.
 - From April 2020 Dec 2020: Mitsubishi Corporation, Nippon Express & Nitori Trading Viet Nam
 - Network & System enhancement project (IT infrastructure & Backup solution);
 - o Microsoft Active Directory migration from Windows server 2003 to 2019 version.
 - From June 2019 April 2020:
 - o Mizuho Bank Viet Nam
 - + New IT infrastructure for Dev & Apps server system project (Server/SAN/Switch & Windows Server System based on MS Hyper-V cluster & Backup solution);
 - + New IT infrastructure for Database server system (MS SQL-HA Always On);
 - + New IT infrastructure for Satellite Office (BCP project).

o Saigon Paper

- + IT infrastructure enhancement for HCM new office project;
- + New Firewall, Domain Controller & Veeam backup server at DR site (Viettel IDC).

o Isuzu Manufacture

- + IT infrastructure enhancement project (New Server/SAN/NAS/FW/Switch & Windows server System based on VMware);
- + New IT Infrastructure for ERP project.
- From April 2019 Feb 2020: Idemitsu Gas Production
 - o Email migration On-premise to MS Office365 (~200 Users) & Email backup solution;
 - Network infrastructure enhancement project (Upgrade all Switch & Server);
 - o Sangfor HCI migration project (Migrate all current physical server & Hyper-V VMs to HCI);
 - HCM Office renovation project (Expand office area).
- From Sep 2018 Feb 2019: MOL Logistic Viet Nam
 - Email migration from local Mail service to MS365 (~190 Users);
 - HCM Office renovation project (Expand server room, office area);
 - o Network & System enhancement for 6 sites (HCM, BD, Tra Vinh, HNI, H.Phong & T.Binh)

Oct 2015 – June 2018: Working at Mitsubishi Electric Viet Nam

- Position: IT Executive;
- Duties: IT Technical support
 - Act as a single point of contact for all user requests, incidents, and general communication at all offices (total ~200 users in HCM main office, Da Nang & Ha Noi branch office);
 - Manage, configure and maintenance all Server system & Network infrastructure (Active Directory, GPO, DNS, DHCP, WDS, DFS, NAS, Symantec Exec Backup, TrendMicro Officescan, Hyper-V, Fortinet, VPN, Leased line/FTTH internet, switch & router system...);
 - o Company Website & Intranet administrator;
 - MS365-Mail exchange, MS Intune administrator;
 - Manage, configure and maintenance all network devices (Printer, AP & Router), PBX & Call center system;
 - Ensure all IT Hardware and software always complied with ISM policy; Training general ISM policy for new employees;
 - o Proposing and purchasing all IT equipment for the Company.

July 2015 - Sep 2015: Working at VietNet Technology Trading Corporation

- Position: Technician;
- **Duties**: Research new devices relating to security systems (access control, CCTV, PBX, Fire alarm & anti-leakage systems: installation, configuration and making User/Admin guide); Company website administrator.

October 2011-April 2014: Working at Environmental Technology Center (ENTEC)

- Position: Environmental Consulting Specialist;
- Duties: Joining to build the Themes, Scientific research projects from provincial level, municipal level, ministerial level and perform the Environmental reports for major partners such as Vedan Viet Nam, Ajinomoto Viet Nam, AB Mauri, Department of Natural Resources and Environment, Department of Trade and Industry, Department of Science & Technology of some provinces in Viet Nam.
 - Manage, purchase and replace machinery and office equipment for the Company.

ACHIEVEMENT

- International certificate: MS Azure Administrator Associate Microsoft Certified;
- International certificate: TOEIC (685 points) Educational Testing Service (ETS);
- Certificate of CCNA, MCSA, MCSE, Microsoft Share Point Nhat Nghe ITC;
- Certificate of Specialist ISO 9001:2011, 14.001:2011 and OHSAS 18001:2011 Institute for Quality Management Viet Nam;
- Certificate of Applied Informatics, Graphics Applications, Application Programming and Website Design -The Informatics Centre University of Sciences, 2009 2011.

SKILLS

- Having knowledge about Smart Home & Security system devices: CCTV, access control system, environmental warning systems...
 - Having knowledge about scripting (batch, powershell), programing (C#, Javascript);
 - Proficiency in technical assembly, installation, maintenance and computer administrator;
 - Being good at self-studying, acquiring, exploiting and testing software quickly;

PERSONALITY DESCRIPTION

- Honest and reliable;
- Sociable and easy-adjusted to work in new environments;
- Working logical, systematic, planned and implemented reasonable jobs;
- Always have passion, ensuring progress of assigned work and have a high responsibility;
- Careful, meticulous, thoughtful and hard-working;
- Agile manners, always calm to handle matters in every situation.

HOBBIES

- Updating new technology and useful applications for work and life;
- Listening to music, playing sports such as football, basketball, badminton and swimming;
- Taking part in social activities.

REFERENCES

(Mr.) Tho, Nguyen Duc

Engineering Division Manager

• 0902.184.068 | ndtho@kddivietnam.com

(Mr.) Thuy, Truong Dac

Presale Division Leader

0934.163.337 | tdthuy@kddivietnam.com